interactive rebase in progress; onto f3db6f3
Last command done (1 command done):
   pick 13a0c1d WIP: Made some local changes
No commands remaining.
You are currently editing a commit while rebasing branch 'main' on 'f3db6f3'.
  (use "git commit --amend" to amend the current commit)
  (use "git rebase --continue" once you are satisfied with your changes)

Untracked files:
  (use "git add <file>..." to include in what will be committed)
	git_status.txt

nothing added to commit but untracked files present (use "git add" to track)
